Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - January 18, 1928: Recital, performed by The Berkshire Playhouse Trio (Box 1)
    - March 4, 1928: Piano Recital, performed by Bruce Simonds (Box 1)
    - March 7-21, 1929: Expositions of Classical and Modern Chamber Music, performed by Manuel Compinsky, Alec Compinsky, Arthur Whiting, John Goss, The New York String Quartet (Box 1)
    - January 20, 1929: Vesper Music, performed by Lucille Reed, Janette Rozene, Frank Rascati, Viola Goulding (Box 1)
    - March 3, 1929: Music for the Harp, performed by Mildred Dilling (Box 1)
    - February 13, 1930: Piano Recital, performed by Gottfried Galston (Box 1)
    - September 30, 1931: Piano Recital, performed by Thomas W. Bussom, Joseph S. Daltry (Box 1)
    - November 15, 1931: Recital, performed by Compinsky Trio (Box 1)
    - November 22, 1931: Piano Recital, performed by Katherine Gorin (Box 1)
    - December 6, 1931: Recital, performed by Thorp McClusky, Joseph S. Daltry (Box 1)
    - January 17, 1932: Songs at the Harp, performed by Margot Jean (Box 1)
    - February 21, 1932: Violin Recital, performed by Harold Berkley (Box 1)
    - March 1, 1932: The Beggar's Opera, performed by The Lyric Theatre of Hammersmith, London (Box 1)
    - March 20, 1932: A Lenten Meditation, performed by Wesleyan Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - November 6, 1932: No title, performed by The Zimmer Harp Trio (Box 1)
    - November 20, 1932: No title, performed by Caroline Thomas (Box 1)
    - December 11, 1932: No title, performed by Manhattan String Quartet (Box 1)
    - January 22, 1933: Song Recital, performed by Inga Hill (Box 1)
    - February 19, 1933: No title, performed by American Woodwind Quintet (Box 1)
    - February 26, 1933: Organ Recital, performed by Joseph S. Daltry (Box 1)
    - May 17, 1933: Song Recital, performed by Virginia E. MacCracken (Box 1)
    - October 29, 1933: Song Recital, performed by Inga Hill (Box 1)
    - November 12, 1933: No title, performed by The Tapley String Quintet (Box 1)
    - November 19, 1933: Violin Recital, performed by Harold Berkley (Box 1)
    - December 10, 1933: Piano Recital, performed by Bruce Simonds (Box 1)
    - December 19, 1933: No title, performed by Middletown Choral Union (Box 1)
    - January 7, 1934: Song Recital, performed by Herbert Wall (Box 1)
    - February 18, 1934: Harp Recital, performed by Mildred Dilling (Box 1)
    - October 7, 1934: No title, performed by The Philharmonic Ensemble (Box 1)
    - October 21, 1934: No title, performed by Josephine Antoine, Frederick Wilkins, Arthur Paggett (Box 1)
    - October 28, 1934: No title, performed by La Forge Spanish Trio (Box 1)
    - November 25, 1934: No title, performed by Manhattan String Quartet (Box 1)
    - April 24, 1935: Piano Recital, performed by Myron D. Casner (Box 1)
    - September 29, 1935:, performed by (Box 1)
    - October 13, 1935: No title, performed by Fernanda Doria, Richard Malaby (Box 1)
    - October 27, 1935: No title, performed by The Van Buren Players of Old Instruments (Box 1)
    - November 10, 1935: No title, performed by Klaus Liwpmann, Charles Posnak (Box 1)
    - November 17, 1935: No title, performed by Astrid Fjelde, Katherine Fjelde Aune (Box 1)
    - May 3-4, 1935: The Pirates of Penzance, performed by Students of Wesleyan University and Mount Holyoke College (Box 1)
    - May 17, 1936: Recital, performed by Mildred Dilling (Box 1)
    - November 15, 1936: No title, performed by Fernanda Doria, Richard Malaby (Box 1)
    - November 22, 1936: No title, performed by Bruce Simonds (Box 1)
    - February 14, 1937: No title, performed by Mabel Deegan (Box 1)
    - April 28th and 30, 1937: The Gondoliers, performed by Undergraduates of St. Joseph College and Wesleyan University (Box 1)
    - October 28, 1937: No title, performed by The Stradivarius Quartet of New York (Box 1)
    - November 17, 1937: No title, performed by Harold Bauer (Box 1)
    - January 13, 1938: No title, performed by The Barrere Ensemble (Box 1)
    - March 4, 1938: Composers Preceding Bach, performed by Charles R. Nicholls, The Cardinals (Box 1)
    - March 11, 1938: Johann Sebastian Bach, performed by Charles R. Nicholls, String Quartet (Box 1)
    - March 18, 1938: Romantic Composers, performed by Charles R. Nicholls, John B. Panknow. (Box 1)
    - March 25, 1938: Cesar Franck, performed by Charles R. Nicholls, Millard S. Thompson (Box 1)
    - April 8, 1938: Modern French Composers, performed by Charles R. Nicholls (Box 1)
    - April 15, 1938: Contemporary American Composers, performed by Charles R. Nicholls, String Quartet (Box 1)
    - May 4, 1938: No title, performed by Howard S. Wilson (Box 1)
    - May 25, 1938: Piano Recital, performed by James R. Johnson, Millard S. Thompson (Box 1)
    - December 6, 1938: No title, performed by Ernst Wolff (Box 1)
    - December 11, 1938: Choir Christmas Concert, performed by Wesleyan Choir (Box 1)
    - January 10, 1939: No title, performed by Roland Hayes (Box 1)
    - February 14, 1939: No title, performed by Rudolph Ganz (Box 1)
    - March 21, 1939: No title, performed by Stradivarius Quartet (Box 1)
    - November 9, 1938: No title, performed by Ernest Krenek (Box 1)
    - March 21, 1939: Lieder Recital, performed by Ernst Wolff (Box 1)
    - April 26, 1939: Piano Recital, performed by E.W. Fischer (Box 1)
    - November 1, 1939: Piano Recital, performed by Egbert W. Fischer (Box 1)
    - October, 1939: Gilbert and Sullivan in Song and Story, performed by Olive Groves, George Baker (Box 1)
    - November 16, 1939: No title, performed by The Stradivarius Quartet of New York (Box 1)
    - December 4, 1939: Monday Club Musical, performed by Bethany Smith, Mrs. Smith, Sue Brainerd, Mary Augusta Daltry, Elva Stearns, Katharine McCurdy, Florence Van Dyke, Diana Daniels, Eva Neumann, Anne Fisher, Lee Reynolds, Jane Moody, Margaret Spaeth, Doris Stearns, Gwendolyn Cowie, Patricia Martin, Janet Thomson, Faith Daltry, Muriel Van Dyke, Sally Goedicke, Jane WIlliamson, Betsy Banks, Lucinda THomson (Box 1)
    - December 7, 1939: No title, performed by Madame Marcelle Denya (Box 1)
    - December 10, 1939: Candle Light Concert, performed by The Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - April 11, 1940: Two-Piano Recital, performed by Bruce Simonds, Rosalind Simonds (Box 1)
    - April 28, 1940: Piano Recital, performed by Ralph Sheldon (Box 1)
    - October 28, 1940: No title, performed by The Maverick Chamber Music Society of Woodstock, NY (Box 1)
    - November 26, 1940: No title, performed by James Friskin (Box 1)
    - December 11, 1940: No title, performed by Gregory Tucker (Box 1)
    - January 14, 1941: No title, performed by Otto Luening, Ethel Luening (Box 1)
    - March 4, 1941: No title, performed by James Sykes (Box 1)
    - April 8, 1941: No title, performed by Arlan Coolidge (Box 1)
    - October 29, 1941: No title, performed by The Manhattan Ensemble (Box 1)
    - February 18, 1942: No title, performed by American Ballad Singers (Box 1)
    - April 23, 1944: Joint Recital, performed by Percy Grainger, Lena Flood (Box 1)
    - December 5, 1944: No title, performed by The Manhattan Trio (Box 1)
    - March 16, (1945?): William Masselos, Pianist, performed by William Masselos (Box 1)
    - October 4, (1945?): Robert Kitain, Violinist, performed by Robert Kitain, Valentin Pavlovsky (Box 1)
    - April 8 (No year): Wesleyan Chamber Music Series, performed by Arlan Coolidge (Box 1)
    - January 25, 1946: Wesleyan University Presents, performed by Barbara Troxell, Bertha Melnik (Box 1)
    - March 5, 1946: Wesleyan University Presents, performed by Ray Lev (Box 1)
    - November 3, 1946: Musical Service, performed by The Wesleyan Chapel Choir, Edward Broadhead, Jean Marie Scholz, William P. Gregory, Wilbur T. Holmes, Golda Shour, George Hecht, Herbert Anderson (Box 1)
    - November 12, 1946: The Roth Quartet, performed by Feri Roth, Sandor Salgo, Jozsef Smilovits, Janos Scholz (Box 1)
    - December 11, 1946: George S. McManus, Pianist, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - December 15, 1946: Candle Light Concert, performed by The Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - January 14, 1947: A Pre-Town Hall Recital, performed by Franco Mannino (Box 1)
    - January 22, 1947: Roland Hayes, Tenor, performed by Roland Hayes, Reginald Boardman (Box 1)
    - February 21, 1947: No title, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - May 9-10, 1947: Two One-Act Comic Operas, performed by The Wesleyan University Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - May 16, 1947: Richard K. Beebe and the Torrington String Quartet, performed by Richard K. Beebe, William Khoury, John Freeman, Elizabeth Beach, Philip Laraia (Box 1)
    - October 3, 1947: No title, performed by Reah Sadowsky (Box 1)
    - November 7, 1947: No title, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - February 12, 1948: No title, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - May 7, 1948: A Recital of Vocal and Instrumental Chamber Music, performed by Samuel C. Silipo, Carl E. Schorske, Wynn E. Westover, Albert G. Sweetser, Kenneth G. Josephson, Betty Sweetser, Ellis B. Kohs, Edward M. Fritz, Norman B. Boothby, Peter P. Komor, David P. McAllester (Box 1)
    - December 14, 1947: Candle Light Concert, performed by The Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - January 9, 1948: Samuel Dushkin, Violin, performed by Samuel Dushkin, Paul Berl (Box 1)
    - February 27, 1948: The Roth Quartet, performed by Feri Roth, Sandor Salgo, Jozsef Smilovits, Janos Scholz (Box 1)
    - October 26, 1948: Charles Panzera, Baritone and Magdeleine Panzera, Pianist, performed by Charles Panzera, Magdeleine Panzera (Box 1)
    - December 7, 1948: Alice Tully, Soprano, performed by Alice Tully, George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - February 22, 1949: The Roth Quartet, performed by Feri Roth, Sandor Salgo, Jozsef Smilovits, Janos Scholz (Box 1)
    - May 5, 1949: Recital, performed by Feorge S. McManus (Box 1)
    - January 11, 1950: George S. McManus, Pianist, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - November 1, 1950: Joint Recital, performed by Ernst Bacon, Analee Camp (Box 1)
    - January 17, 1951: The Hartford Symphony Orchestra, performed by George Heck, Bela Urban, Hartford Symphony Orchestra (Box 1)
    - March 7, 1951: George S. McManus, Pianist, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - April 25, 1951: A Recital of Woodwind and Brass Music, performed by Ann Creswell, Richard K. Winslow, Frederick Habenicht, Gordon Eaton, John Wood, Sanford Fraser, Vincent Allison, Richard Maxwell, Philip Church, Elliot Maxwell, Jack Lerner, Richard France, Donald Watt, John Collier, Roy Dunhanm, Rober Mack, James Plimpton, Richard Winslow (Box 1)
    - May 23, 1951: The Julliard String Quartet, performed by Robert Mann, Raphael Hillyer, Robert Koff, Arthur Winograd (Box 1)
    - May 14, 1952: George S. McManus, Pianist, performed by George S. McManus (Box 1)
    - November 3, 1952: The Hartford Symphony Orchestra, performed by George Heck, Hartford Symphony Orchestra (Box 1)
    - November 19, 1952: New Art Wind Quintet, performed by Andrew Lolya, Irving Neidich, Melvin Kaplan, Tina di Dario, Elizabeth Bobo (Box 1)
    - April 12, 1953: No title, performed by The Wesleyan University Instrumental Ensemble, Leonard Felberg, Louis Catuogno, Richard K. Winslow (Box 1)
    - October 21, 1953: No title, performed by Pro Musica Antiqua (Box 1)
    - November 23, 1953: No title, performed by Budapest String Quartet (Box 1)
    - January 27, 1954: No title, performed by Hans Hotter, Baritone (Box 1)
    - March 10, 1954: No title, performed by Szymon Golberg, Violinist (Box 1)
    - May 5, 1954: No title, performed by Raymond Rendall, Pianist (Box 1)
    - October 20, 1954: No title, performed by Quartetto Italiano (Box 1)
    - October 19, 1955: Elisabeth Schwarzkopf, Soprano, performed by Elisabeth Schwarzkopf, Paul Ulanowsky (Box 1)
    - November 30, 1955: The Alfred Deller Trio, performed by Alfred Deller, Desmond Dupre, Robert Conant (Box 1)
    - December 7, 1955: A Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - January 11, 1956: James Wolfe, Pianist, performed by James Wolfe (Box 1)
    - February 22, 1956: Hungarian Quartet, performed by Zoltan Szekely, Alexandre Moskowsky, Denes Koromzay, Vilmos Palotai (Box 1)
    - March 14, 1956: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Fred Prentice, Raymond Rendall, Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - March 21, 1956: Andres Segovia, Guitarist, performed by Andres Segovia (Box 1)
    - April 25, 1956: The Wesleyan University String Quartet, performed by David Spencer '57, Russell Snyder '57, Roger Turkington '58, Arthur Lessing '58 (Box 1)
    - May 16, 1956: Raymond Hanson and Leonard Seeber, Pianists, performed by Ramond Hanson, Leonard Seeber (Box 1)
    - July 11, 1956: The Wesleyan University String Quartet, performed by Wesleyan University String Quartet, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - July 18, 1956: Betty Allen, Mezzo-Soprano, performed by Betty Allen, Jonathan Brice (Box 1)
    - July 25, 1956: Joyce Flissler, Violinist, performed by Joyce Flissler, Norman Johnson (Box 1)
    - August 1, 1956: The Chanticleers, performed by William Diard, Raymond Keast, Richard Wright, James Martindale, Kenneth McGuire (Box 1)
    - August 8, 1956: Raymond Rendall, Pianist, performed by Raymond Rendall, Pianist (Box 1)
    - November 1, 1956: The Golden Age Singers of London, performed by Golden Age Singers (Box 1)
    - November 28, 1956: Raymond Rendall, Pianist, performed by Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - January 16-17, 1957: The Julliard String Quartet, performed by Julliard String Quartet (Box 1)
    - February 20, 1957: The Vienna Octet, performed by Vienna Octet (Box 1)
    - March 20, 1957: Robert McFerrin, Baritone, performed by Robert McFerrin (Box 1)
    - July 24, 1957: Fools, Feuds, and Furriners, performed by Irene Bewley (Box 1)
    - July 10, 1957: The Barri Opera Company, performed by Richard Barri, Maria Restova, Helen Spina, Grace Lang, Robert Sommer, Anthony Christoforo (Box 1)
    - May 28, 1957: Organ Recital, performed by James Dalton (Box 1)
    - May 12, 1957: Choral Service, performed by Colby Chapel Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society (Box 1)
    - May 11, 1957: Joint Concert, performed by Middletown Women's Chorus, Wesleyan Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - May 8, 1957: The Wesleyan University String Quartet, performed by David Spencer '57, Russell Snyder '57, Roger Turkington '58, Arthur Lessing '58 (Box 1)
    - April 28, 1957: Choral Vespers, performed by Wesleyan University Choral Society, Colby Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - April 26, 1957: Joint Concert, performed by Centenary Singers, Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 24, 1957: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - April 21, 1957: Delta Kappa Epsilon Concert Series, performed by George Coffee '60, Roger Turkington '58, David Spencer '57, Arthur Lessing '58, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - April 10, 1957: The Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 9, 1957: Wesleyan University Glee Club Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 8, 1957: No title, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club, University of Maryland Women's Chorus (Box 1)
    - April 7, 1957: The Tenth Annual Memorial Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 29, 1957: Wesleyan University Glee Club Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 24, 1957: Choral Service, performed by Bryn Mawr College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society (Box 1)
    - March 21, 1957: The Wesleyan University String Quartet, performed by David Spencer '57, Russell Snyder '57, Roger Turkington '58, Arthur Lessing '58 (Box 1)
    - March 22, 1957: No title, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 16, 1957: Choral Concert, performed by Smith College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society (Box 1)
    - March 10, 1957: Delta Kappa Epsilon Concert Series, performed by Wesleyan University Brass Quartet (Box 1)
    - March 1, 1957: Prom Concert, performed by Wesleyan Univerisity Glee Club (Box 1)
    - February 24, 1957: Delta Kappa Epsilon Concert Series, performed by Richard Donohue, Anna Doering, Ronald Klinker (Box 1)
    - July 31, 1957: A Program of Folk Songs and Ballads, performed by Marjorie Rice Daltry (Box 1)
    - August 7, 1957: The Bergen Chamer Ensemble, performed by Robert Weinrebe, Napoleon Cerminara, Isabel Weinrebe (Box 1)
    - October 23, 1957: The Albeneri Trio, performed by Ward Davenny, Giorgio Ciompi, Benar Heifetz (Box 1)
    - November 13, 1957: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Gerard Jaffe, Raymond Rendall, Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - November 25, 1957: Rita Streich, Soprano, performed by Rita Streich, Paul Ulanowsky (Box 1)
    - December 8, 1957: Candlelight Service, performed by Smith College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society (Box 1)
    - December 15, 1957: Christmas Vespers, performed by Smith College Choir and Chamber Orchestra, Wesleyan University Choral Society (Box 1)
    - January 9, 1957: Virtuosi di Roma, performed by Riccardo Castagnone, Alberto Poltronieri, Luigi Ferro, Renato Ruotolo, Franco Gulli, Alfredo Sabbandini, Edmondo Malanotte, Aleardo Savelli, Benedetto Mazzacurati, Antonio Valisi, Guido Mozzato, Renato Zanfini Salvatore Pitzianti (Box 1)
    - February 12, 1958: Raymond Rendall, Pianist, performed by Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - February 22, 1958: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - February 22, 1958: The Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 2, 1958: Gerard Souzay Internationally Renowned Baritone, performed by Gerard Souzay (Box 1)
    - March 1, 1958: The Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 2, 1958: No title, performed by Jon Magendanz '61, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - March 2, 1958: Lenten Vesper Services, performed by Wesleyan Choral Society, Colby Chapel Choir (Box 1)
    - March 7, 1958: Prom Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - March 14, 1958: Concert by Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 8, 1958: Wesleyan University Glee Club Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 9, 1958: The Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 10, 1958: The Wesleyan University Glee Club, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 13, 1958: No title, performed by Richard Donohue '58, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - April 17, 1958: No title, performed by Roberta Sterne, Colin Sterne (Box 1)
    - April 20, 1958: Choral Service, performed by Vassar College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society, Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - April 27, 1958: The E. Harold Geer Memorial Concert, performed by Vassar College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society, Orchestra of Students from the Juilliard School of Music (Box 1)
    - April 30, 1958: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Martha Monroe, Roger Turkington '58, Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - May 8, 1958: William Dale, Pianist, performed by William Dale (Box 1)
    - July 3, 1958: Robert McFerrin, Baritone, performed by Robert McFerrin, Norman Johnson (Box 1)
    - November 9, 1958: No title, performed by Connecticut College Choir, Wesleyan University Choral Society, Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, Paul L. Thomas (Box 1)
    - November 19, 1958: The Janacek Quartet, performed by Jiri Travnicek, Jiri Kratochvil, Adolf Sykora, Karel Krafka (Box 1)
    - November 5, 1958: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra (Box 1)
    - May 14, 1958: The New York Brass Quintet, performed by Robert Nagel, Frederick Schmidt, John Glasel, Erwin Price, Harvey Phillips (Box 1)
    - May 17, 1958: No title, performed by Roger Turkington '58, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - June 5-6, 1959: The Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra, Singers from the Choral Society and Glee Club (Box 1)
    - November 30, 1962: The Singing Boys of Mexico, performed by Morelian Boy's Choir (Box 1)
    - October 23, 1958: Early German Baroque Music, performed by New York Pro Musica (Box 1)
    - November 17, 1962: Julius Katchen, Pianist, performed by Julius Katchen (Box 1)
    - January 9, 1963: Budapest String Quartet, performed by Budapest String Quartet (Box 1)
    - February 6, 1963: Mattiwilda Dobbs, Soprano, performed by Mattiwilda Dobbs (Box 1)
    - October 13, 1964: Ravi Shankar, Sitarist, performed by Ravi Shankar (Box 1)
    - November 11, 1964: Cesare Valletti, Tenor, performed by Cesare Valletti (Box 1)
    - January 9, 1965: Juilliard String Quartet, performed by Juilliard String Quartet (Box 1)
    - February 3, 1965: Julian Bream, Lutenist and Guitarist, performed by Julian Bream (Box 1)
    - March 22, 1965: New York Pro Musica, performed by New York Pro Musica (Box 1)
    - November 6, 1964: The Wesleyan University String Quartet, performed by Wesleyan University String Quartet (Box 1)
    - November 22, 1964: Bertram Turetzky, Bassist and Ensemble, performed by Bertram Turetzky (Box 1)
    - December 6, 1964: Standards of Operatic Performance in England and in America, performed by Harold Rosenthal (Box 1)
    - February 7, 1965: John Fenstermaker, Organist, performed by John Fenstermaker (Box 1)
    - March 7, 1965: Robert Loud, Folk Singer, performed by Robert Loud (Box 1)
    - May 2, 1965: Isaac Hurwitz, Violin and Raymond Rendall, Piano, performed by Isaac Hurwitz, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - January 13, 1965: The Wesleyan University String Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University String Orchestra (Box 1)
    - February 21, 1965: The Play of Daniel, performed by Wesleyan University Glee Club, Wheaton College Glee Club (Box 1)
    - April 14, 1965: The Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra (Box 1)
    - May 9, 1965: Richard Hartzell, Bass-Baritone, Raymond Rendall, Piano, performed by Richard Hartzell, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - May 16, 1965: Piano Recital, performed by William F. Brooks '65 (Box 1)
    - October 1, 1965: Academic Chorus, University of Skoje, Yugoslavia, performed by Academic Chorus "Mirce Acev" (Box 1)
    - October 15, 1965: Ruggiero Ricci, Violinist, performed by Ruggiero Ricci (Box 1)
    - October 1, 1965: Balasarasvati, performed by Bharata Natyam (Box 1)
    - November 12, 1965: The Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra (Box 1)
    - December 5, 1965: Richard Provost, Guitarist, performed by Richard Provost (Box 1)
    - December 8, 1965: Student Recital, performed by Peter Johnson, John Basinger, Kenrick Day, Thomas Etkin, John Andrews, David Minugh, Raymond Rendall (Box 1)
    - January 16, 1966: John Fenstermaker, Organist, performed by John Fenstermaker (Box 2)
    - February 17, 1966: Shinichi Yuize, Koto, performed by Shinichi Yuize (Box 2)
    - March 6, 1966: Von der Mehden String Quartet, performed by Von der Mehden String Quartet (Box 2)
    - April 17, 1966: Isaac Hurwitz, Violin and Raymond Rendall, Piano, performed by Isaac Hurwitz, Raymond Rendall (Box 2)
    - November 16, 1965: Marilyn Horne, Soprano, performed by Marilyn Horne (Box 2)